/* eslint-disable no-unused-vars */
export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which luxury watch brand is known for the Royal Oak series?",
    option1: "Patek Philippe",
    option2: "Rolex",
    option3: "Audemars Piguet",
    option4: "Omega",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which watch brand is famous for the 'Submariner' model?",
    option1: "Tag Heuer",
    option2: "Rolex",
    option3: "Audemars Piguet",
    option4: "Longines",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What brand makes the Nautilus, a luxury sports watch?",
    option1: "Patek Philippe",
    option2: "Breitling",
    option3: "Panerai",
    option4: "Cartier",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which brand is known for extremely high-priced and limited edition models like the RM 56-02 Sapphire?",
    option1: "Richard Mille",
    option2: "Omega",
    option3: "Seiko",
    option4: "Hublot",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which brand made the first wristwatch in history?",
    option1: "Cartier",
    option2: "Rolex",
    option3: "Omega",
    option4: "Patek Philippe",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which brand has the crown logo?",
    option1: "Rolex",
    option2: "Audemars Piguet",
    option3: "Patek Philippe",
    option4: "Omega",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which watch brand is associated with James Bond?",
    option1: "Breitling",
    option2: "Omega",
    option3: "Rolex",
    option4: "Cartier",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which luxury brand makes the Big Bang collection?",
    option1: "Hublot",
    option2: "Tag Heuer",
    option3: "Rolex",
    option4: "Seiko",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which brand produced the Sky-Dweller and Daytona models?",
    option1: "Omega",
    option2: "Tag Heuer",
    option3: "Rolex",
    option4: "Panerai",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Swiss luxury brand is known for the Grandmaster Chime 6300A, the most expensive wristwatch ever sold?",
    option1: "Richard Mille",
    option2: "Audemars Piguet",
    option3: "Rolex",
    option4: "Patek Philippe",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which brand uses the term 'Haute Horlogerie' in its philosophy?",
    option1: "Audemars Piguet",
    option2: "Casio",
    option3: "Citizen",
    option4: "Timex",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which luxury brand made the 'Tourbillon with Three Gold Bridges'?",
    option1: "Breguet",
    option2: "Girard-Perregaux",
    option3: "Jaeger-LeCoultre",
    option4: "Montblanc",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following watches is often referred to as an 'entry-level luxury' Rolex?",
    option1: "Daytona",
    option2: "Datejust",
    option3: "Sky-Dweller",
    option4: "Yacht-Master",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which luxury brand is known for watches that use sapphire crystal cases?",
    option1: "Richard Mille",
    option2: "Omega",
    option3: "Tissot",
    option4: "Longines",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which watch brand introduced the Co-Axial escapement technology?",
    option1: "Breitling",
    option2: "Omega",
    option3: "Rolex",
    option4: "Cartier",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which brand's watches are tested at the COSC (Contrôle Officiel Suisse des Chronomètres) for chronometer certification?",
    option1: "Omega",
    option2: "Tag Heuer",
    option3: "Rolex",
    option4: "Both Omega and Rolex",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which luxury brand often names models after classical musicians like 'Lange 1' and 'Zeitwerk'?",
    option1: "A. Lange & Söhne",
    option2: "Rolex",
    option3: "Cartier",
    option4: "Richard Mille",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which company produces the Speedmaster Moonwatch?",
    option1: "Tag Heuer",
    option2: "Rolex",
    option3: "Omega",
    option4: "Patek Philippe",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which brand’s motto is 'You never actually own a Patek Philippe'?",
    option1: "Rolex",
    option2: "Patek Philippe",
    option3: "AP",
    option4: "Hublot",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which luxury watch brand originated in 1839 in Geneva, Switzerland?",
    option1: "Omega",
    option2: "Audemars Piguet",
    option3: "Patek Philippe",
    option4: "Tag Heuer",
    ans: 3,
  },
];
